{
    "questions": [
    {
        "question": "Good morning John. How are you?",
        "answers": [
            "I'm fine, thank you.",
            "I'm going by train.",
            "My name's John.",
            "I will be there"
        ],
        "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "How many resorts do you work with?",
        "answers": [
            "Unfortunately, we don't have the ressources now.",
            "We work with five different ski resorts.",
            "We have twenty people on staff at the moment.",
            "This is our last resort."
        ],
        "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Do we know what happened to Nancy yesterday?",
        "answers": [
            "She wrote down a list of instructions.",
            "They say she retired last week.",
            "She said she felt a pain in her chest, then passed out.",
            "I will see her tomorrow."
        ],
        "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you cope with hiring so much new staff?",
        "answers": [
            "We don't do it ourselves, we outsource it to an agency.",
            "We only recuited two people last year.",
            "Our recruitement officer retired last year.",
            "I was recruited by this company."
        ],
        "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Why don't you get a new car?",
        "answers": [
            "It's a Toyota.",
            "We hired it at the airport.",
            "We can't afford to.",
            "It is my niece's car."
        ],
        "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Did you have to fire anyone recently?",
        "answers": [
            "There was a big fire at the warehouse yesterday.",
            "We hired ten new people in the past few months.",
            "We laid off several factory workers only last week.",
            "My uncle is a fireman."
        ],
        "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "How often do you fly to Argentina?",
        "answers": [
            "It takes three and a half hours.",
            "I'm afraid all flights are fully booked.",
            "Argentina is a beautiful country.",
            "About twice a month."
        ],
        "correctIndex": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "How many students actually pay for their own tuition?",
        "answers": [
            "The tuition fee is over fifty thousands dollars.",
            "Not many, most of them have a corporate scholarship.",
            "There is a high failure rate, only eighty-five percent graduated last year.",
            "Students are really hard working."
        ],
        "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is John doing with his feet propped up on his desk?",
        "answers": [
            "He is expecting an important meeting.",
            "He doesn't want anybody to see his shoes.",
            "He is relaxing after a delicious meal.",
            "This is John's desk."
        ],
        "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Were you a fan of Flash Gordon when you were a child?",
        "answers": [
            "Not really.",
            "He certainly was.",
            "Oh yes I am.",
            "He was gone in a flash."
        ],
        "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Why has Peter dropped out?",
        "answers": [
            "It's too heavy.",
            "He has come to talk to us about cost-saving.",
            "He's got a really busy schedule.",
            "Peter is coming out."
        ],
        "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What has been your biggest challenge?",
        "answers": [
            "Meeting the deadline. We had a very tight schedule.",
            "I'm looking forward to doing a full-sized opera next year.",
            "We will take part in the European contest.",
            "The prize is very large."
        ],
        "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "How much does your son have to pay in tuition fees?",
        "answers": [
            "The airfare was 35 dollars.",
            "Nothing. His company is paying for his studies.",
            "He pays 500 dollars in income tax.",
            "He is enrolled in a prestigious school."
        ],
        "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Be careful, the boxes are dirty and some of them have sharp edges.",
        "answers": [
            "I have never boxed before.",
            "Don't worry. I'm used to lifting heavy boxes.",
            "I'll wash it first.",
            "It's okay. I'll put these gloves on."
        ],
        "correctIndex": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of goods do they sell?",
        "answers": [
            "Mostly luxury items.",
            "They made a good profit last year.",
            "Everything is on sale.",
            "Everything is quite good here."
        ],
        "correctIndex": 1
    }
]}